University of Connecticut 1998.0186
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series III: Wallace Moreland Files, 1964-1972
  - Health Center, 1956-1964 (Box 183:, Folder 3458-3482)
  - Citizens Committee for a Connecticut Medical-Dental School (Box 184:, Folder 3483-3484)
  - Pharmacy, School of, 1963-1964 (Box 184:, Folder 3485)
  - Physical Therapy, School of, 1963-1964 (Box 184:, Folder 3486)
  - UConn Admissions policy - problems and public relation (Box 184:, Folder 3487)
  - Medical School, 1964 (Box 184:, Folder 3488)
  - Health Center (Box 184:, Folder 3489-3496)
  - Connecticut Academy of General Practice, 1964 (Box 184:, Folder 3497)
  - Nursing, School of (Box 184:, Folder 3498)
  - North-End Project
    - Warehouse (Box 184:, Folder 3499-3528)
    - Family and home program (Box 184:, Folder 3529-3532)
    - Greater Hartford Chamber of Commerce (Box 184:, Folder 3533-3538)
    - Noyes, Richard, C. (Vice Pres. Manufacturing Association of Hartford County) (Box 184:, Folder 3539)
    - The North End of Hartford (Mr. Moreland's copy) (Box 184:, Folder 3540)
    - Current and Past Programs - Proposed new inner-city program (Box 184:, Folder 3541)
    - Daycare Centers Sub-committee (Dr. Keller) (Box 184:, Folder 3542)
    - Film Project (Box 184:, Folder 3543)
    - Health and Home Care Sub-committee (Dean Patterson) (Box 184:, Folder 3544)
    - Replies from Deans (Box 184:, Folder 3545)
    - Project Co-op (Box 184:, Folder 3546)
    - Jones, Le Roy (Commissioner, Department of Community Affairs) (Box 184:, Folder 3547)
    - Atkins, William H. - Family (Box 184:, Folder 3548)
    - Bodine, Thomas (Box 184:, Folder 3549)
    - Davis, Jack - North Hartford report (Box 184:, Folder 3550)
    - Community Renewal team of Greater Hartford, (2 folders) (Box 184:, Folder 3551)
    - North Hartford News Releases (Box 184:, Folder 3552)
    - Ms. Ray - Mrs. Lane - Group in President's Garden (Box 184:, Folder 3553)
    - North Hartford business (Box 184:, Folder 3554)
    - Dean Sacks - Human Rights Commission Summer Program (Box 184:, Folder 3555)
    - Employment Committee - University of Hartford (Dean Menke, chairman) (Box 184:, Folder 3556)
    - Ballard Puppets - Showmobile (Box 184:, Folder 3557)
    - Dr. Mackellar's report on proposed nutritional survey for Hartford (Box 184:, Folder 3558)
    - University of Connecticut Welfare Sub-committee (Dean Trecker) (Box 184:, Folder 3559)
    - School of Education proposals (Box 184:, Folder 3560)
    - Education Committee ( Ralph William, chairman) (Box 184:, Folder 3561)
    - Dean Harvey (Box 184:, Folder 3562)
    - 4-H Garden Club programs (Box 184:, Folder 3563)
    - Concerts for disadvantaged at Auditorium (Box 184:, Folder 3564)
    - Goddard Space Flight Center (Box 184:, Folder 3565)
    - Job opportunity pledge program (Box 184:, Folder 3566)
    - Job Development Center, Employment Center (Box 184:, Folder 3567)
    - Model cities program ( John Letai) (Box 184:, Folder 3568)
    - Proposed Police Training program (Box 184:, Folder 3569)
    - Vine Street Property (Box 184:, Folder 3570)
    - Violence (Box 184:, Folder 3571)
    - Follow-up (Box 184:, Folder 3572)
    - Rutgers material (Box 184:, Folder 3573)
    - South Arsenal Neighborhood Progress Center (Box 184:, Folder 3574)
    - Lease signing, Warehouse (Box 184:, Folder 3575)
    - Ebony Businessmen's League (Box 184:, Folder 3576)
    - Neighborhood Legal Service ( Sydney T. Schulman) (Box 184:, Folder 3577)
    - SAUC - Follow-up (Box 184:, Folder 3578)
    - Neighborhood Council Chairmen (Box 184:, Folder 3579)
- Series IV: Special Committee on Placement, 1966-1969
  - 1966-1969 (Box 1998-0183_1)
    Scope and Contents note
    Notes, Administrative Records, Correspondence, Newspaper Clippings [Subjects include: Committee Correspondence, Committee on Student Conduct, Placement Committee.]